Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Archives Personal Files, 1824-present UA.Personal.Files
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- C
  - Cain, Lester J.
  - Cain, Thomas
  - Cake, Cathleen
  - Cale, Edgar B. *
  - Caldwell, Denise
  - Calhoun, Captain *
  - Caliendo, Eugene L.
  - Caliguri, Richard
  - Calipari, John
  - Call, Russell D.
  - Callanen, Frank J.
  - Callaway, Clifton
  - Callihan, Hubert D.
  - Calvert, John *
  - Calvert, Monte A.
  - Camblon, Ruth Bartholomew
  - Cameron, John R.
  - Cameron, Judy
  - Cameron, Ronald G.
  - Cameron-Sanlon, Karen
  - Camillus, John C.
  - Camp, Kimberly
  - Campbell, Bebe Moore
  - Campbell, Bill
  - Campbell, Charles G.
  - Campbell, David N.
  - Campbell, Iain
  - Campbell, Jackie
  - Campbell, James McLean
  - Campbell, John E.
  - Campbell, Judith *
  - Campbell, Robert David
  - Campbell, Shirley
  - Campbell, Susan
  - Campesino, Sara-Claire
  - Canady, Jerome
  - Canfield, F. Curtis *
  - Cannon, Fergus (class of 1825)
  - Cano, Elmer *
  - Cano, Juan
  - Cantekin, Erem I.
  - Cantini, Virgil (oversize) *
  - Cantor, Norman L.
  - Cao, M.
  - Capanosa, R. J. *
  - Capatch, P. William
  - Capelli, Christopher
  - Capitano, Blair
  - Capitman, William G. *
  - Caplan, Arthur
  - Caplan, Louis *
  - Caplan, Paul
  - Caplan, Ron
  - Capo, Rosemary
  - Capp, Michael
  - Cappy, Ralph J.
  - Capretto, Robert
  - Carapucci, Lauren
  - Capson, Carol A.
  - Caraway, Doug
  - Carbaugh, Doal
  - Carbo, Toni *
  - Carcaise, Connie
  - Cardona, Rudolfo *
  - Carell, Edgar F. *
  - Carey, Larry C.
  - Carey, William C.
  - Carhart, Daniel *
  - Carhart, David
  - Caritis, Steve N.
  - Carlisle, Ronald A.
  - Carlson, H. C. (oversize) *
  - Carlos, Timothy
  - Carlson, Charles (Rev.)
  - Carlson, Lindsay
  - Carlson, Richard O. *
  - Carlson, Robert E. *
  - Carlton, Stephen E.
  - Carnahan, Judith
  - Carnahan, Robert Brown *
  - Carnegie, Andrew *
  - Carnevali, Patrician Gay
  - Carpenter, Charli
  - Carpenter, Doug
  - Carpenter, R. Charku
  - Carpenter, Rhys *
  - Carpenter, Robert R.
  - Carr, Becky
  - Carr, Brian
  - Carr, Jean Ferguson
  - Carr, Patricia B.
  - Carr, Ramona
  - Carr, Stephen
  - Carrasco, Mary
  - Carrau, Ricardo L.
  - Carrier, Julie
  - Carrizales, Marco
  - Carroll, Donald
  - Carroll, Edward J.
  - Carroll, Holbert N. (Dr.)
  - Carson, Anne
  - Carson, Walter Page
  - Carter, Bernard A. *
  - Carter, Cameron S.
  - Carter, Carol
  - Carter, Carolyn McCraw *
  - Carter, Franklin Wood
  - Carter, James C.
  - Carter, Mark T.
  - Carter, Melanie
  - Carter, Philippa
  - Carter, Robert L.
  - Carter, Robin
  - Carter, Ruth *
  - Carthew, Richard
  - Cartier, Jennifer
  - Carts, Norman (Dr.)
  - Cartwright, Carol A.
  - Cartwright, Nancy
  - Cartwright, Thomas E.
  - Carvell, George
  - Carver, Frank (oversize) *
  - Carver, George (oversize) *
  - Casanova, Len
  - Cascio, Michael
  - Casey, Dennis
  - Casey, Robert P., Jr.
  - Cashdollar, Margaret (Dr.)
  - Cashman, B. Z.
  - Caskey, S. W.
  - Cass, Carl B.
  - Cass, Stephen
  - Cassaro, James P.
  - Cassell, Frank
  - Cassetori, Michael
  - Cassiano, Richard
  - Cassidy, Marian
  - Cassidy, William (oversize) *
  - Cassidy-Schall, Laura
  - Cassing, James H.
  - Cassing, Jim
  - Cassoni, Leonard W.
  - Castillo, Wilfrido *
  - Castner, Michael F.
  - Catalano, Aileen
  - Catekin, Erdem
  - Catterjee, Rabikar
  - Cauley, Jane
  - Caulkins, Jonathan
  - Cauna, Nikelajs
  - Cavalla, Joseph
  - Cavanaugh, Matt *
  - Cavanaugh, Philips
  - Cave, M. Donald
  - Cavoukian, Raffi
  - Cecconi, Lou (Bimbo)
  - Cederstrom-Huston, Erika
  - Celona, John
  - Cepull, Jeff
  - Cercone, David
  - Cerney, Maureen
  - Cerniglia, Nikki
  - Chabon, Michael *
  - Chabotar, Samantha
  - Chaffee, Ellen E.
  - Chaily, Seoil
  - Chakravarti, Aravinda
  - Chalker, Justin
  - Chamallas, Martha
  - Chamberlain, Bobby S.
  - Chambers, Bernice Gertrude
  - Chambers, Edward
  - Chambers, George
  - Chambers, Guinevere S.
  - Chambers, Joan
  - Chambers, Will Grant *
  - Chambers, William
  - Champagne, Audrey
  - Champagne, Blaise
  - Champagne, David (Dr.)
  - Champion, David
  - Chancellor, Michael
  - Chandrasekhar, S. (Dr.)
  - Chan, I-Ja *
  - Chang, H. K.
  - Chang, Judy
  - Chang, Lillian
  - Chang, Paul
  - Chang, Shi-Kuo
  - Chang, Shiao-Hung
  - Chang, Yang
  - Chang, Yuan
  - Chanillo, Sagun
  - Chanin, Gerald
  - Channing, Cornelia Post
  - Chao, Chong-Yun
  - Chaon, Dan
  - Chapman, Deborah L.
  - Chapman, Diwana
  - Chapman, Guy P.
  - Chapman, Janet
  - Chapman, John W. *
  - Chapman, Wendy
  - Chappano, Paul J.
  - Chappel, Dean
  - Charley, Michael R. *
  - Charlton, Sam *
  - Charters, W. W.
  - Charron-Prochownick, Denise
  - Chasar, Dwight W.
  - Chase, Jonathan M.
  - Chastek, Gary
  - Chattopadnyay, P. K.
  - Chaun, Chih (Dr.)
  - Chauss, A. Alice *
  - Chav, Teresa Ree
  - Checkley, Tom
  - Cheever, Daniel S. *
  - Cheever, Francis *
  - Chekan, Dave
  - Chen, James *
  - Chen, Kan *
  - Chen, Kevin
  - Chen, Shih-Chuan
  - Chen, Yong-Zhuo
  - Chenault, Joann
  - Ch'eng, I-fan
  - Cheng, Kenneth
  - Cheng, Shi-Yuan
  - Cheng, Tao
  - Cheong, Fiona
  - Chergi, Christine A.
  - Cherniavsky, Michael
  - Cherpes, Thomas L.
  - Cherry, Dinol
  - Chervenick, Paul *
  - Chesler, Herbert
  - Chestnutwood, Linda
  - Chetlin, Milton A.
  - Chew, Daniel
  - Chew, Douglas
  - Chew, Pat
  - Chez, Ronald A.
  - Chi, George Y. H.
  - Chi, Michelene T.
  - Chiang, John
  - Chiang, Robert
  - Chiang, Shiao-Hung
  - Chiang, Yee
  - Chiappetta, Laurel
  - Chiarulli, Don
  - Chidi, Alexis
  - Childers, Bruce R.
  - Childs, Elizabeth R.
  - Chin, Sue-Moy
  - Chinite, Benjamin *
  - Chipman, Roy
  - Chisum, Donald S.
  - Chiu, Chao-Lin
  - Chontos, Stephen A.
  - Choate, John I. M.
  - Choi, Augustine
  - Choma, John, Jr.
  - Chou, S. H. *
  - Chow, Carson
  - Choyke, Wolfgang
  - Christian, Jim
  - Christiano, J. G.
  - Christman, Raymond R.
  - Christmas, Raven
  - Christopher, Dean
  - Christopher, Karen
  - Chritchfield, Jack B.
  - Chronister, Guy L. (Dr.)
  - Chrysanthis, Panos
  - Chu, Constance
  - Chu, Charleen T.
  - Chu, Lee (Dr.)
  - Chu, S. C.
  - Chu, Wen-djang (Dr.)
  - Chung, Albert E. (Dr.)
  - Churchill, Chris
  - Chute, Shirley B.
  - Chworsky, Martin Philip
  - Chyongchiou, Jeng Lin
  - Chyu, Minking
  - Ciacchella, Sebastian
  - Cichowicz, Ron
  - Cignetti, Curt
  - Ciocco, Antonio *
  - Cisneros, Jose
  - Citeroni, William R., Jr.
  - Citton, Yves
  - Clancy, Sam
  - Clapp, Frederick Mortimer *
  - Clapp, George Hubbard *
  - Clare, Beth
  - Clare, David W. (Dr.)
  - Clark, C. Reynolds
  - Clark, Dean A.
  - Clark, Duncan B.
  - Clark, E. Bruce
  - Clark, G. Reynolds
  - Clark, Lynette V.
  - Clark, Marc
  - Clark, Rasheed
  - Clark, Raymond W. (Rev.)
  - Clark, Renee M.
  - Clark, Richard P.
  - Clark, Robert A.
  - Clark, William
  - Clark, William W.
  - Clarke, Duncan
  - Clarke, James F. *
  - Clarke, Richard
  - Clarke, Theodore H.
  - Clarke, Torie
  - Claus, Edward P. (Dr.)
  - Claus, Joanne
  - Clause, William L.
  - Clay, Lucius *
  - Claycamp, Rebecca
  - Cleary, Sherry M.
  - Clelan, Wilfred
  - Cleland, David I.
  - Cleland, Donald *
  - Cleland, Hugh G. *
  - Clemens, Daryl F.
  - Cleven, Nels Andrew Nelson
  - Clevenger, Theodore, Jr.
  - Clifton, Charles
  - Clifton, Rob
  - Clinton, Michael
  - Clinton, Thomas
  - Clochesy, John
  - Cloonan, Michele V.
  - Clothey, Frederick
  - Clothier, Robert C. *
  - Clough, Evalyn
  - Coalson, Rob
  - Coates, Penelope
  - Coates, Robert S.
  - Cobb, James T.
  - Coben, Jeffrey H.
  - Coble, Charles "Ray" (Dr.) *
  - Coble, Patricia A.
  - Cobucci, Dolores A.
  - Coburn, Cynthia
  - Cochran, Jerome
  - Cochran, William
  - Cochrane, Charles (Dr.)
  - Cockerill, Eleanor *
  - Coe, Charlie
  - Coe, Charlotte (Dr.)
  - Coetzee, Johannes
  - Coffee, Carole
  - Coffey, Joseph I.
  - Coffey, Maryann B.
  - Coffin, Charles R.
  - Coffin, William Carey
  - Coffman, A. W.
  - Coffman, William P.
  - Cogan, Morris L. *
  - Coghill, Lynn
  - Cohen, Alvin J. *
  - Cohen, Bernard *
  - Cohen, Cliff
  - Cohen, David
  - Cohen, Henry B.
  - Cohen, Howard
  - Cohen, Jacob (Dr.)
  - Cohen, Jonathan
  - Cohen, Judith A.
  - Cohen, Martin P.
  - Cohen, Moshe
  - Cohen, Peter Z.
  - Cohen, Randy
  - Cohen, Richard L.
  - Cohen, Rosalie (Dr.)
  - Cohen, Stanford I.
  - Cohen, Susan M.
  - Cohen, Theodore (Dr.)
  - Cohick, Keith
  - Cohn, Alvin J.
  - Cohn, Elizabeth L.
  - Cohn, Major
  - Cohoe, B. A.
  - Cohon, Jared
  - Cohouet, Frank V.
  - Colaezzi, John L.
  - Colamarino, Brant
  - Colangelo, Joseph, Jr.
  - Colavita, Frank B. *
  - Colbert-Lewis, Danielle
  - Colby, Carl
  - Colclaser, R. Gerald
  - Cole, David
  - Cole, Kelly Stefano
  - Cole, Lauri
  - Colella, D. Samuel
  - Coleman, Ayana
  - Coleman, Francis J. (Dr.)
  - Coleman, Harry
  - Coleman, Morton
  - Coleman, Richard C.
  - Coleman, Ronald
  - Coleman, Stephen
  - Coleman, Thomas
  - Coleman, W. Stephen "Alex"
  - Coles, Nicholas J.
  - Coles, William, Jr.
  - Colker, Ruth
  - Collier, Shelton
  - Collin, Ben
  - Collins, Chuck
  - Collins, Dwight
  - Collins, Henry Homer
  - Collins, James
  - Collins, Kathryn
  - Collins, Kevin
  - Collins, Mark
  - Collins, Michael W.
  - Collins, Mickey
  - Colmenares, Augusto
  - Colodny, Robert (oversize)
  - Colton, Donald (Dr.)
  - Colwell, Alexander H.
  - Colwell, Richard
  - Colwell, Robert P.
  - Combellack, Frederick M.
  - Comfort, Louise K.
  - Comfort, Robert W. *
  - Comella, Mark
  - Commager, Henry Steele *
  - Conant, Roger T.
  - Conbescot, Monique
  - Concha, Felix
  - Condee, Nancy
  - Condo, Jean
  - Condon, Edward U.
  - Condon, William S.
  - Conigliaro, Joseph
  - Conley, Dalton
  - Conley, John
  - Conn, Carlyle
  - Conn, John F.
  - Connamacher, Martha
  - Connamacher, William
  - Connell, Frances J.
  - Conner, Mary K.
  - Conners, C. Keith
  - Conniff, William P.
  - Connolly, Andrew
  - Connolly, J. Wray
  - Connoly, George
  - Connor, Bernadette (Dr.)
  - Connor, Mary E.
  - Connor, Sharon E.
  - Conomikes, John G.
  - Conrad, Kathryn
  - Conrad, Kirk P.
  - Constable, Nicole
  - Constandy, Harry
  - Constantine, Gregory
  - Constantino, Joseph
  - Constantino, Rose E.
  - Constanty, Joseph
  - Conte, Samuel D.
  - Conti, Jason
  - Conti, Stephen F.
  - Contreras, Mathilda (Dr.)
  - Conturo, William E. *
  - Converse, Paul D.
  - Conway, James C.
  - Cook, Allen
  - Cook, Caroll "Beano" (oversize) *
  - Cook, D. Ryan
  - Cook, Leland W.
  - Cook, Robert F.
  - Cook, Robert L.
  - Cook, Steven
  - Cooke, Edward F. *
  - Cooley, Charles *
  - Cooley, Thomas M.
  - Cooley, William W.
  - Coon, Darryl
  - Cooper, Charles
  - Cooper, Gregory
  - Cooper, John Madison
  - Cooper, Kenneth F.
  - Cooper, Lynn
  - Cooper, Mabel
  - Cooper, N. John
  - Cooper, Rory
  - Cooper, Terrance
  - Cooper, Wade
  - Cooper, William Hamley *
  - Cooper, William L. *
  - Cooper, William M., MD
  - Cope, Myron
  - Copeland, Ben
  - Copeland, John Wilson *
  - Copperman, Philip
  - Coppersmith, W. Lewis
  - Coppock, Paul
  - Corbett, Margaret Mary
  - Corbett, Patti
  - Corcoran, Timothy E.
  - Corletti, Michael A.
  - Corn, Morton
  - Cornelius, David
  - Cornell, Clare
  - Correa, Hector *
  - Corry, Charles A.
  - Corry, Robert J.
  - Cort, Robert
  - Corwin, Harry O.
  - Coryell, Larry
  - Cosby, Attila
  - Cosby, Bill
  - Coss, Raymond L. *
  - Cost, Charles L.
  - Costa-Grelo, Maria
  - Costacou, Tina
  - Costain, W. Douglas
  - Costantino, Joseph
  - Costello, Elizabeth
  - Cothran, Mary
  - Cottam, Richard (oversize) *
  - Cotter, Kevin
  - Cottereau, Carrie
  - Coughenour, Tory
  - Coughlin, Thomas S.
  - Coulehan, Jack
  - Coulehan, John
  - Coull, Bruce M.
  - Coull, James (oversize)*
  - Coulson, John
  - Coulter, E. Merton
  - Counihan, Peter J.
  - Counts, George S. *
  - Courcoulas, Anita
  - Covarrubias, Alicia
  - Covert, Jimbo
  - Covert, Margaret E. *
  - Cowell, Ronald
  - Cowgill, Ursula M.
  - Cowles, John T. (Dr.)
  - Cox, Aletta
  - Cox, Catherine
  - Cox, Gerald J.
  - Cox, Richard C. *
  - Cox, Richard J. *
  - Cox, Robert (Dr.) *
  - Cox, Torrie
  - Coyer, Larry
  - Coyle, Beverly G.
  - Coyle, Richard *
  - Coyle, William *
  - Crabtree, James A. *
  - Craft, James A. *
  - Crafts, William *
  - Craig, Cheryl Allen
  - Craig, David *
  - Craig, David Rankin
  - Craig, James C.
  - Craig, John
  - Craig, Neville B. (oversize) *
  - Craig, Raymond
  - Craig, Sam B.
  - Craig, Sam B., Jr. (Dr.)
  - Craig, Steve
  - Craig, William N.
  - Crain, Susan L.
  - Cramblet, Ruth *
  - Crane, Judson A.
  - Crary, Penny
  - Crary, Ryland W. (Dr.) *
  - Craven, Bryan
  - Craven, Wes
  - Cravener, Gary
  - Crawford, Alexander Wellington *
  - Crawford, James T.
  - Crawford, John David
  - Crawford, Stanton C. (oversize) *
  - Crawford, William
  - Crean, Tom
  - Crecca, Joe
  - Creek, Roy J.
  - Creighton, L. W. *
  - Creinin, Mitchell
  - Creshkoff, Ajay J. *
  - Cress, Dean
  - Cretcher, Leonard H.
  - Criep, Leo H. (Dr.)
  - Crippen, David
  - Critchfield, Jack B. *
  - Croce, Pat
  - Crochunis, Vince
  - Croco, Carlton W.
  - Croft, Barbara
  - Croft, Jean Ann
  - Croghan, Major *
  - Cromie, Mark
  - Cromwell, Dewitt P.
  - Cronaver, Adrian
  - Croskey, Joseph
  - Cross, James S.
  - Cross, Janet Stillinger
  - Cross, Paul (Dr.)
  - Cross, Richard J. (Dr.)
  - Crossette, Barbara
  - Crossley, Mary A.
  - Crossman, David *
  - Crouch, George W. *
  - Crouch, Michael
  - Croup, A. H.
  - Crow, Charles *
  - Crow, John
  - Crow, Terry *
  - Crowell, John Franklin
  - Crowley, Kevin
  - Crown, David A.
  - Crozier, Alfred
  - Crozier, Lucille B. *
  - Cuansing, Eduardo
  - Cubelic, Charles R.
  - Culbertson, George *
  - Cullen, Charles
  - Culver, Montgomery Morton
  - Culver, Monty *
  - Cully, William
  - Cummings, Josh
  - Cummings, Vonteego
  - Cummins, K. W.
  - Cummins, Walt
  - Cunningham, James
  - Cunningham, James V.
  - Cunningham, Richard
  - Cuomo, Mario
  - Curie, Marie
  - Curran, Dennis P.
  - Curran, James Joseph
  - Curran, John
  - Curran, Ronald (Dr.)
  - Curran, Stephen
  - Curran, Vivian
  - Currie, Brainerd *
  - Currie, Melvin (Dr.)
  - Curry, E. Thayer (Dr.)
  - Curry, Kenneth V.
  - Curry, Nancy Ellen
  - Curry, Richard
  - Curthoys, Norman P. *
  - Curtin, Hugh
  - Curtis, Ford E. *
  - Curtis, Frank J.
  - Curtis, Heber D. *
  - Curtiss, Ed
  - Cutler, John C.
  - Cutler, John C. (Mrs.)
  - Cuane, Judson A. *
  - Cyert, Richard
  - Cypress, H. Raymond
  - Czak, Fran
  - Czarnecki, Jill
  - Czarnecki, Leo
- D
  - Dadio, Louis "Bill"
  - Dadlani, Sara
  - Daehnick, Wilfried (Dr.) *
  - Daer, Hank
  - Dahl, Leo P. (Major General) *
  - Dahl, Ronald E.
  - Dai, Fuling
  - Dai, Lo-Sheng
  - Dailys, Jay E. (Dr.)
  - D'Alessandris, Joe
  - Dalessandris, David A.
  - Daley, Dennis C.
  - Daley, Kerry
  - Dailey, John Thomas
  - D'Alonzo, Frank
  - Dameshek, H. Lee (Dr.)
  - Damian, Victor
  - D'Amico, Frank
  - Damski, Tom
  - Dane, John Hunter
  - Daniel, Jack
  - Daniel, Jerlean
  - Daniel, Z. K.
  - Daniel, Zaccheus
  - Daniels, Linda R.
  - Danielson, Michelle E.
  - Daniewski, Wlodzimierz
  - Danishefsky, Samuel *
  - Danowski, Thaddeus S. *
  - Dansbury, Merianne
  - Danse, L. O.
  - Dansro, Roy
  - D'Antonio, Joyce A.
  - Dantry, Jay
  - D'Appollonia, Ariane C.
  - Dapprich, A. E.
  - Darbaker, Leasure K.
  - Darby, Joseph *
  - Darling, Jon
  - Darlington, Mary O'Hara *
  - Darlington, William M.
  - Darragh, John
  - Darrah, Charles
  - Darrall, Clyde H.
  - Darsh, Allan L.
  - Daubert, B. F.
  - Daubert, B. F. (oversize) *
  - Daufenbach, William L.
  - Daugherty, Carroll R.
  - Daugherty, Nikki
  - Dave, Amish J.
  - Davenport, Judith
  - Davey, Thomas J. *
  - David, Elwood Craig
  - David, Mary Elizabeth
  - Davidoff, Susan
  - Davidson, Cliff
  - Davidson, James M.
  - Davidson, Lynda
  - Davies, Paul
  - Davies, Thomas J.
  - Davin, Eroc Leif
  - Davis, Adena Johnson
  - Davis, Angela
  - Davis, Bernard B.
  - Davis, Christine J.
  - Davis, Devra
  - Davis, Diane
  - Davis, Ed *
  - Davis, Elwood C. (Dr.)
  - Davis, Eugene
  - Davis, Florence
  - Davis, Fran
  - Davis, Joyce N.
  - Davis, Larry E.
  - Davis, Nancy Barber
  - Davis, Natalie *
  - Davis, Nathan
  - Davis, Paula
  - Davis, Peter J. *
  - Davis, Robert H.
  - Davis, S. B.
  - Dawida, Mike
  - Dawson, Barton H.
  - Dawson, L. P. *
  - Day, Billy
  - Day, Ken
  - Day, Lowell
  - Day, Nancy L.
  - Day, Ralph
  - Day, Richard L. (Dr.)
  - Deal, Bryan
  - Dean, Howard
  - Dean, Philotus *
  - Deangelis, Catherine
  - DeArdo, Anthony
  - Deasy, Phyllis
  - DeBolt, Greg
  - Debons, Anthony
  - Debrah, Dan
  - Debski, Richard Eric
  - DeCarlo, Charley R. *
  - Decastro-Sallis, Kishma
  - Decato, Todd
  - Deck, Leland *
  - Decker, H. Ryerson
  - DeComo, Peter
  - DeCreus, An
  - Dede, Christopher
  - Deep, Sam
  - Dees, Charles R.
  - DeFazio, David J.
  - DeFigio, Nicholas (Dr.)
  - DeFriese, Gordon H.
  - Degennaro, Alan
  - DeGood, Douglas
  - DeGroat, John
  - DeGroat, William C. (Dr.)
  - DeGroote, Melvin
  - Dehn, Heinz
  - Deible, Christopher
  - Deitrick, Dick
  - Deitrick, Sabina
  - DeJong, David
  - DeJonge, Joost H. Kiewiet (Dr.)
  - DeKeyser, Robert
  - DeKosky, Steven T.
  - Delaney, Charles MacGregor
  - DeLaney, John F., Jr.
  - Delaney, John T.
  - Delaney, Timothy R.
  - Delany, William
  - Delbridge, Theodore R.
  - DeLeo, Emil *
  - Delgado, Richard
  - Delitto, Anthony
  - Dellaverson, John
  - Del-Nido, Pedro J.
  - Delson, Eric
  - DeLuca, Neal
  - DeMart, Herbert
  - Demas, Vida Kramer (SEE Kramer, Vida)
  - Demetkis, Yuri
  - Demmler, Oscar
  - DeMontmollin, Oliver
  - Demster, Alexander
  - Deng, Jau-Shyong *
  - Deng, Simon
  - Denman, Loretta (Dr.)
  - Denman, Mary Thompson (Mrs. David) *
  - Dennehy, Dan
  - Dennis, Wayne (Dr.)
  - Denny, Donald
  - Denny, Ebenezer
  - Denova, Rebecca
  - Dent, James Norman (oversize)
  - Dent, John A.
  - Denton, Frank (oversize) *
  - DeNunzio, Anthony
  - DePasqua, Carl *
  - Derbyshire, Stuart
  - Derbies, Mahmound K.
  - DeRemer *
  - Derrick, Patty
  - Derricotte, Toi
  - DeRubertis, Frederick R. *
  - Desantis, Joe
  - Desarro, Andrea
  - DeSilva, Padma
  - DeSilver, Cohen
  - DeSilvio, Dominic
  - DesIslets, Colbert Mousseau
  - Deskins, Barbara
  - Deskins, Wilber E.
  - Desmond, Richard, PhD
  - DeSua, Frank
  - Detlefsen, Ellen Gay *
  - Detre, Katherine M.
  - Detre, Thomas P.
  - Detwiler, Kate
  - Deutch, Melvin
  - Devine, Katie
  - Devita, Michael
  - DeVitis, Michael
  - DeVitto, John
  - Devlin, Bernie
  - DeVoe, Jan R.
  - DeVries, Egbert
  - Dew, Mary Amanda
  - DeWald, Ernest T. *
  - DeWalt, Billie R.
  - DeWalt, Kathleen
  - Dewey, Edward Russell
  - Dewey, Fred A. (Dr.)
  - DeWitt, Kristina
  - Dhaliwal, Deepinder
  - Dhaliwal, Tanvir
  - DiBasi, Holly
  - Dice, Helen Frost (oversize) *
  - Dice, J. Howard
  - DiCiccio, Carmen
  - DiCio, Nick
  - Dickens, Mike
  - Dicker, Jonathan
  - Dickerson, Linda A.
  - Dickey, P. A.
  - Dickinson, John T.
  - Dickinson, Steve
  - Dickson, Joseph Z.
  - Dickson, Q. Todd
  - Dicola, Brad
  - DiConstanzo, James L.
  - Dieckmann, Herbert
  - Dieffenbach, George
  - Diesendruck, Thmar
  - Dietrich, Leah A.
  - Dietrich, William S.
  - DiFazio, John
  - Dignam, James J.
  - DiLeo, Mrs. *
  - Diller, Theodore
  - Dillion, Richard J. *
  - DiMaria, Francesca
  - DiMartino, Elena
  - DiMattio, Tony
  - Dimitrov, Nikola
  - Dimmick, Mary Laverne
  - Dines, Edward A. *
  - Dinker, John D.
  - Dinkins, D. J.
  - Dinman, Bertram D.
  - Dionne, E. J., Jr.
  - DiPalma, Allen A.
  - Diran, Adekanye Dee
  - Disque, Thomas Lawrence (Dr.)
  - Distelhorst, Carl F.
  - Ditka, Mike *
  - D'Itri, Julie
  - Dittert, Lewis W. *
  - Dively, George S. *
  - Diven, Warren
  - Divens, William C., Jr.
  - Dixit, Balwant N.
  - Dixon, Bettina
  - Dixon, Frank James *
  - Dixon, Jamie
  - Dixon, Norman R. *
  - Dixon, Russell A. *
  - Dizard, Rachael
  - Doan, Dan
  - Dobbs, Clifton *
  - Dobda, Deborah
  - Dobler, Bruce
  - Dodds, Christopher V.
  - Dodds, John Wendell *
  - Dodds, Kenneth D.
  - Doerfler, Leo G.
  - Doll, Becky
  - Doll, Edgar A. (Dr.) *
  - Doll, Zach
  - Dominy, Phillip
  - Domke, Herbert R. (Dr.)
  - Donaghey, Charles E. *
  - Donahoe, Michael
  - Donahue, Jack
  - Donahue, Joseph
  - Donahue, Thomas M. *
  - Donaldson, John C. (Dr.)
  - Donaldson, Robert
  - Donaldson, Sam
  - Donaldson, William F. (Dr.)
  - Donatelli, Frank
  - Donato, Richard
  - Doncaster, William
  - Donenberg, Vera
  - Dong, Mai-Li *
  - Donham, Dennis E.
  - Donington, Robert
  - Donley, Rosemary
  - Donnenberg, Vera S.
  - Donnorummo, Robert
  - Donny, Eric
  - Donoghue, Timothy R.
  - Donorio, Anthony D., Jr.
  - Donovan, John
  - Doody, Mary Ann *
  - Dorer, Rae
  - Dorin, Tamica
  - Dorman, Janice
  - Dorn, Lorah
  - Dorn, Sarah B.
  - Dornie, Fr. Ivan
  - Dorow, Ernest B.
  - Dorrance, Graeme
  - Dorrill, William *
  - Dorsett, Anthony D.
  - Dorsey, Bob Rawls *
  - Dorsey, Doreen *
  - Dorsey, Harry N. *
  - Dorsky, Julian
  - Doswell, Willa M.
  - Doty, Mark
  - Doubleday, Douglas Jay
  - Dougherty, Andrew J. (Lieutenant Colonel) *
  - Dougherty, George
  - Douglas, Bodie Eugene
  - Douglas, Charles McKenna
  - Douglas, Daphine
  - Douglas, Ellen
  - Douglas, Herb
  - Douglass, P. C. (oversize) *
  - Dourando, Damian
  - Douthett, Samuel (class of 1831)
  - Doutt, Margaret T. *
  - Dowbenko, Kateryna
  - Dowd, Paul (Dr.)
  - Dowiak, Miles
  - Downey, Khiawatha
  - Downey, Thomas B.
  - Doyle, Grace H.
  - Doyle, Jamar
  - Drabecki, J. Katherine
  - Drake, Miriam A.
  - Draovich, Pete
  - Drapanas, Theodore (Dr.) *
  - Drash, Allen L. *
  - Drayer, David
  - Drauss, Frank *
  - Drennan, Robert D.
  - Drescher, Seymour
  - Dresser, Miles
  - Drew, Frances *
  - Drew, Regan
  - Driesen, Judith *
  - Drisko, Richard (Dr.)
  - Drosness, Daniel L. (Dr.)
  - Drum, Gary G.
  - Druzdzel, Marek Jozef
  - Dryer, Bernard V. (Dr.)
  - Dryland-Vig, Katherine
  - Duane-Lennard, Catherin
  - Du, Wu
  - Dube, Sanjay
  - Duca, Zoraida
  - Ducanis, Alex J.
  - Ducazeaux, Eliane
  - Ducker, Jack
  - Duda, Robert
  - Dudley, Edward *
  - Duecker, Werner W.
  - Duensing, Stefan
  - Duerr, Richard
  - Duff, James H. *
  - Duff, John Milton *
  - Duff, Joseph M.
  - Duff, Ogle Burks
  - Duffus, Emily Hall
  - Duffy, John
  - Dufour, Charles
  - Dugan, Ann M.
  - Duggar, George S. *
  - Dugdale, Richard C. (Dr.)
  - Duino, Russell A.
  - Duker, Georgia
  - Dukes, Charlene Mickens
  - Dull, Malcolm *
  - Dumas, John C.
  - Dunbar-Jacob, Jacqueline
  - Dunbrook, Raymond F.
  - Duncan, Edgar N.
  - Duncan, Elizabeth E.
  - Duncan, Robert Kennedy
  - Duncan, William S. (Dr.)
  - Dunkelberger, Tobias *
  - Dunkelman, Robert
  - Dunlap, Robert (Rev.) *
  - Dunlop, David L.
  - Dunmire, Susan
  - Dunn, James Crerar
  - Dunn, James P. (Dr.)
  - Dunn, William
  - Dunn, William IV (Dr.)
  - Dupertius, S. Milton (Dr.)
  - Durant, Joseph, Jr.
  - Duratz, James
  - Durocher, Roy T. (Dr.)
  - Durrant, John
  - Dury, Tim
  - Duschl, Richard
  - Dusenberry, William Howard
  - Dutkovich, Frank M., Jr.
  - Dutton, Joseph *
  - Dwyer, Jim
  - Dwyer, John Herrington (Dr.) *
  - Dwyer, Mavourneen
  - Dwyer, Thomas
  - Dyboski, Roman
  - Dyche, Howard E.
  - Dyer, Herman *
  - Dyer, Kelly
  - Dyess, George McKallip *
  - Dykstra, Ann Marie
  - Dym, Eleanor *
  - Dzirkalis, Andrew
  - D'zmura, A. P.
- E
  - Eagles, Eldon L. (Dr.)
  - Eagles, Juanita (Dr.)
  - Eagon, Patricia
  - Eakin, Laurabelle
  - Eapen, A. Thomas
  - Earhart, Amelia
  - Earhart, Will
  - Earl, Chantee
  - Earl, David
  - Earle, George H.
  - Earley, L. W. *
  - Earley, Tony
  - Earls, Christopher J.
  - Earman, John S.
  - Easter, Jennifer
  - Eastman, C. R.
  - Eatman, Rodney
  - Eaton, H. N.
  - Eaton, Joseph (Dr.) (oversize)
  - Ebberts, Alfred R.
  - Ebenbach, David Harris
  - Ebenezer, Denny
  - Eberle, Elmer
  - Eberly, Robert E., Jr.
  - Ebert, Nicole